<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE xliff PUBLIC "-//XLIFF//DTD XLIFF//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/committees/xliff/documents/xliff.dtd" >
<xliff version="1.0">
  <file original="global" source-language="en" datatype="plaintext">
    <header/>
    <body>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Signin</source>
        <target>Entrar</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Forgot your password?</source>
        <target>¿Olvidaste tu contraseña?</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Create My Account</source>
        <target>Registrarme</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>sign in</source>
        <target>Entrar</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>request</source>
        <target>Registrarme</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Thank you for applying for an account. You will receive a verification
email shortly. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check 
your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>Gracias por registrarte en Tirengarfio. Recibirás un e-mail para completar tu registro. Si no encuentras el e-mail en la bandeja de entrada, revisa tu carpeta "spam".</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Forgot your password? No problem! Just enter your email address and click "Reset My Password." You will receive an email message containing a link permitting you to change your password if you wish.</source>
        <target>¿Has olvidado tu contraseña? Para que crear una nueva, introduce tu direccion de e-mail y presiona sobre "Nueva contraseña". A continuacion te enviaremos un e-mail para que generes tu nueva contraseña.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>That account was never verified. You must verify the account before you can log in or, if
necessary, reset the password. We have resent your verification email, which contains
instructions to verify your account. If you do not see that email, please be sure to check 
your "spam" or "bulk" folder.</source>
        <target>No confirmaste tu registro. Para confirmar el registro debes abrir el e-mail que te enviamos y seguir las instrucciones. Si el e-mail no aparece en la bandeja de entrada comprueba la carpeta "spam".</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Thank you for confirming your account! You are now logged into the site.</source>
        <target>¡Gracias por confirmar tu registro! Estas logeado en Tirengarfio.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>That confirmation code is invalid. 
        </source>
        <target>Registrarme</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Reset My Password</source>
        <target>Nueva contraseña</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Thanks for confirming your email address. You may now change your
password using the form below.</source>
        <target>Gracias por confirmar tu dirección de e-mail. Ahora puedes cambiar tu password.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Your password has been successfully reset. You are now logged in to this site. In the future, be sure to log in with your new password.</source>
        <target>Has cambiado tu contraseña. Ahora estas dentro de Tirengarfio. A partir de ahora utiliza tu nueva contraseña para autenticarte.</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
For security reasons, a confirmation message has been sent to 
the email address associated with this account. Please check your
email for that message. You will need to click on a link provided
in that email in order to change your password. If you do not see
the message, be sure to check your "spam" and "bulk" email folders.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
We apologize for the inconvenience.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;Por razones de seguridad, te hemos enviado un
                mensaje a tu cuenta de correo para que puedas cambiar
                tu contraseña. Necesitarás pinchar sobre un enlace que 
                contiene dicho e-mail. Si no encuentras el mensaje en
                tu bandeja de entrada comprueba tu carpeta "spam". &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Sentimos el inconveniente.
&lt;/p&gt; 
         </target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>&lt;p&gt;
That confirmation code is invalid.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
This may be because you have already confirmed your account. If so,
just click on the "Log In" button to log in.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Other possible explanations:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
1. If you copied and pasted the URL from
your confirmation email, please make sure you did so correctly and
completely.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
2. If you received this confirmation email a long time ago
and never confirmed your account, it is possible that your account has
been purged from the system. In that case, you should simply apply
for a new account.
&lt;/p&gt;</source>
        <target>&lt;p&gt;No podemos confirmar tu registro.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Puede ser debido a que ya has confirmado tu cuenta. En ese caso, pincha 
        sobre el boton de "Log in" para entrar en Tirengarfio.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Otra causas pueden ser:&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;1. Si copiaste y pegaste la URL del e-mail que te enviamos, asegurate que seleccionaste la URL entera.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;2. Si recibiste el email hace mucho tiempo, es posible que tu cuenta haya sido cancelada.
         En ese caso registrate de nuevo.&lt;/p&gt;</target>
      </trans-unit>
      <trans-unit>
        <source>Continue</source>
        <target>Continuar</target>
      </trans-unit>      
    </body>
  </file>
</xliff>